Rebuilding is a drama film directed by Max Walker-Silverman.
After wildfires take his ranch, a cowboy named Dusty winds up in a FEMA camp, finding
community with others who lost homes, including his daughter and ex-wife.
Dusty, played by Josh O'Connor.
Ruby, played by Meghann Fahy.
Callie Rose, played by Lily LaTorre.
Mila, played by Kali Reis.
Bess, played by Amy Madigan.
Mr. Cassidy, played by Jefferson Mays.
Rebuilding is a 2025 American neo-Western-drama film written and directed by Max Walker-Silverman
starring Josh O'Connor, Lily LaTorre, Meghann Fahy, Kali Reis and Amy Madigan.
It had its world premiere at the 2025 Sundance Film Festival on January 26,
2025, and was released on November 14, 2025, by Bleecker Street.
The film explores themes of colorado, cowboy, ex spouses,
father daughter relationship, resilience.
The tone is emotional.